e-rewards.com 2015-12-25

# e-Rewards Opinion Panel | Privacy Policy

Our site's registration form requires you to give us enrollment contact information (your full name, postcode, date of birth, email address, and number of emails desired to be received in a week). This information is compulsory to be able to register you as a Member of the Research Now program. If you fail to provide this information, you will be unable to enroll in the Research Now program.

However, it is optional for you to provide demographic profile data (like occupation, travel frequency, and areas of interest). Failing to provide this information will not preclude you from participating in the Research Now program; however, it is encouraged so you can receive a more personalized experience on our site. Specifically, we use this data to customize and tailor your experience with the Research Now program, the application and website, showing you content in which you may be interested and displaying content according to your preferences. Additionally, we use this data to enable the fielding of market research studies and reserve the right to share it in anonymous singular summary and aggregate form with third parties for this purpose.

Anonymous Singular Summary and Aggregate Statistical Information

Personal demographic and profile data regarding our Members is only shared with our Partners and other third parties on an anonymous singular summary basis or an aggregate basis. Anonymous singular summary information is data that describes the interest profile and demographics data of a Research Now Member without specifically identifying the Member. For example, this data does not contain personally identifying information such as a name or email address, nor does the combination of data make it possible to identify you. Aggregate information is data that describes the interest profiles and demographics of Research Now Members as a group (in the aggregate) without specifically identifying any single Member who helps comprise that group. This data also does not contain personally identifying information such as a name or email address but describes group interest profiles (for example, car brand preferences of Research Now Members as a group) and group demographic information (for example, the average age of Research Now Members as a group).

Personally Identifiable Information

Research Now may provide personally identifiable information to our Partners, our Reward Partners, our Panel Partners, our Marketing Partners, our Clients and third parties for, including, without limitation, the following purposes: (i) the augmentation of Member information with statistical information available from a third party, (ii) independent auditing and/or verification of respondent data for quality control purposes, and (iii) the suppression of Member contact information from email communications that a Member has not consented to receiving.

When our Partners, our Reward Partners, our Panel Partners, our Marketing Partners, our Clients and other third parties receive personally identifiable information from Research Now, they are required to sign legally binding agreements that hold them accountable to the Council of American Survey Research Organization's ("CASRO") "Standards Regarding Disclosure of Respondent-Identifiable Data to Clients." By entering into this agreement with Research Now, our Partners, our Panel Partners, our Marketing Partners, our Rewards Partners, our Clients and other third parties agree that their use of survey response data will be limited to research purposes and that all personally identifiable information will remain confidential. Unless you provide prior consent, personally identifiable information that is shared with our Partners, Reward Partners, Panel Partners, Marketing Partners, Clients and other third parties will not be transmitted to further parties and will not be used in conjunction with sales and/or marketing communications or promotions.

We do not share, sell, rent or trade personally identifiable information with third parties for their promotional purposes.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website. 

In the event that Research Now goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email or prominent notice on our website for thirty (30) days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

Surveys

Research Now may invite you to participate in online surveys. The information requested in these surveys may include, but is not limited to, your opinions, purchase history, and purchase intent regarding consumer and/or business products and services. These surveys may also request information defined as sensitive (e.g. data directly or indirectly revealing racial and ethnic origins, political, philosophical or religious opinions, trade union affiliation, health or sexual life). Again, you are not required to provide us with this information if you do not want to and failing to provide this information will not preclude you from participating in the Research Now program. The information collected by these surveys is used in connection with Research Now market research sponsored by third-party companies and by Research Now to customize and tailor your experience with the Research Now program, the application and website. We reserve the right to share this information in an anonymous singular summary and aggregate form with third parties for this purpose.

Your Electronic Relationship with Our Partners

If you allow us to do so by checking the corresponding box on the Member registration form and/or Welcome Gift selection form, we will share select enrollment information, including your full name, postcode and your email address, with the Partner who invited you into the program and the Partner from whom you selected a Welcome Gift. If you so desire, this will enable you to foster a relationship with the Partners and receive electronic communications from them. While we enter into partnership agreements only with major brands that undertake to respect our Members' privacy, Research Now will not be responsible for our Partners' actions concerning your information.

Agents/Service Providers

We use other third parties, such as a fulfillment company, to fulfill gift card redemptions. When you redeem for a gift card, we will share your name and address as necessary for the third party to provide that service. This third party is prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for promotional purposes.

Member-Get-A-Member

If you are selected to use our referral service to invite a friend to join Research Now, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send you a one-time email to forward, inviting him or her to join Research Now. Research Now stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us to request that we remove this information from our database.

Contests

From time to time, Research Now and/or third parties in cooperation with Research Now may sponsor sweepstakes and contests on this site and, as a result, may request information from you for participation purposes. Your participation in these contests is completely voluntary and you have the choice of whether to disclose this information. Such information will be used by Research Now to notify the winners and award prizes. Also, we reserve the right to share this information in an anonymous singular summary and aggregate form with third parties.

Supplemental Information

In order to provide survey opportunities to you, we may on occasion supplement the personally identifiable information you submitted to us with information from third party sources.

**ID Verification**  
We may use a third party supplier to verify your identity as stipulated in the ISO 26362 standard for access panels. 
**Enhancement of Profile Information**  
We purchase marketing data from third parties and add it to our existing user database to provide enriched analytical data for our clients' use. While this marketing data will be associated with personally identifiable information within the Research Now system, we will obtain your explicit approval to release personally identifiable information to our clients. Otherwise, all personally identifiable information is removed from the marketing data before the marketing data is provided to any client. 
**Log Files**  
As true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in secure log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, Internet service providers (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating systems, date/time stamps and/or clickstream data. Of this automatically collected data, only the IP address is linked to your personally identifiable information. We use the log files for security purposes to help protect our systems. 

Research Now's Use of Cookies

A cookie is simply a small text file containing information about the user that is placed by a website on the user's hard drive. Research Now places persistent cookies, java, scripts or tags on your computer when you complete the registration form or log into the Research Now website, and places a session cookie on your computer while you are participating in a survey or viewing the Research Now website without logging in. Persistent cookies are used to store your email address and encrypted password. Research Now uses this cookie to recognize you when you visit our website so that we may provide you with customized pages based on information in your Member account or profile. This cookie is also required to log in and view Member-specific information on the website. Research Now uses session cookies to maintain your session state across user requests. This type of cookie is used to record when you complete a survey, how much of the survey you complete, the country you are viewing and what language you are using to view the website. We may also use cookies to track certain information about you based upon your activity on our site or on a third party's site. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our site or not), what browser you are using, and your IP address. We use this information to conduct internal research on our Members' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand and serve our Members. We do not associate information stored in our cookies to personally identifiable information you submit to us while using the Research Now website. Research Now occasionally utilizes email Web beacons to monitor email deliverability. We reserve the right to share this information in an anonymous singular summary and aggregate form with third parties.

From time to time, we may allow a third-party media service to display content on our site. These third-party media services may use cookies within their content (e.g., to analyze trends, administer some part of the site, track users' movements, etc.), but we have no access to or control over these cookies. The use of cookies by these third parties shall be governed by their respective privacy policies. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

You can refuse to accept cookies, free of charge, by adjusting the privacy settings of your Web browser software. However, if you do not allow cookies from Research Now, you may not be able to use all of the features on this website.

Advanced Cookies

The advanced cookie tracks the online patterns of Research Now Members. The advanced cookie, which may be placed by Research Now or in conjunction with a third party, incorporates a key which can identify tags contained in certain online content relating to our clients and their products and services.

If a Research Now Member views a page containing any content that includes the tag, the key will send Research Now an update confirming that the Member has viewed the page containing this content.

In addition, some advanced cookies can be used to target you with advertisement related to research for ad-effectiveness. These advertisements will only be displayed for research purposes and not for Research Now-specific advertising or advertising campaigns unrelated to a specific research projects.

Certain Web pages or Web-based advertisements that you view may be tagged by Research Now, and in some cases, data collected on tagged content may be combined with survey answers that you provide. For example, when you visit or click on our third-party partners' Web sites or online advertisements these events are recorded by Research Now or one of our technology partners, which in turn reports the data to us. We provide that data directly, or combine it with the other information that you provide us with, such as your survey responses and demographic information (but not with your personally identifiable information), to provide market research analysis and data delivery services to our clients, technology partners, and/or Rewards Partners and Marketing Partners. You can opt out of our technology partners' own data collection and ad targeting [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp), [here](http://aboutads.info/choices) or [here](http://preferences.truste.com/truste). If you delete cookies on your browser after opting out, you will have to opt out again.

You can opt out of receiving such advanced cookies on your device via Research Now by updating your preferences on your Research Now account preferences page. Our advanced cookies will not track members who are under eighteen (18) years of age. Of course, if a cookie is one that a Research Now Member may receive from a third party, regardless of the Member's participation in the Research Now program, then opting out with Research Now will not prevent the Member from receiving that third party's cookie. We neither have access to, nor control over, third-party cookies or how they may be used. Likewise, if the cookie is placed by a third party, we have no control over the nature of the content with which these tags are included. If you would like more information about third-party use of cookies and about your option not to accept these cookies, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). Your access to our websites and/or application will not be affected if you do not accept cookies placed by third parties.

**The table below shows Advanced Cookies we use:**

Vendor | Domain | Cookie-Name  
---|---|---  
Drawbridge ([opt-out](http://www.drawbrid.ge/optoutstart)) | adsymptotic.com | U  
Quantcast ([opt-out](https://www.quantcast.com/company/opt-out)) | quantserve.com | d, mc, sq  
Research Now (opt-out) | researchnow.com | adsp  
Rocket Fuel ([opt-out](http://rocketfuel.com/opting-out)) | rfihub.com | e, hl, rud, ruds  
Dynamic Logic ([opt-out](http://www.safecount.net/viewyourcookiesinformation_optinout.php)) | questionmarket.com | cs1, ES, panel  
Neustar ([opt-out](https://www.neustar.biz/privacy/opt-out)) | adadvisor.net | ab  
Liveramp ([opt-out](http://liveramp.com/opt_out/)) | rlcdn.com | ck1, rlas3, rtn1, dids1265407297  
  
Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

Our third party tracking utility partner employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our Members’ personally identifiable information. 

Other Websites

This site may contain links to other Internet sites that are not operated or controlled by Research Now. We cannot control and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

Non-Electronic Communications with You

In addition, we occasionally may employ other companies to perform Welcome Gift or Reward fulfillment mailings on our behalf. They may have access to the personal information needed to fulfill their functions, but may not use it for any other purposes.

Social Media Features and Widgets

This site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook 'Like' button and Widgets, such as the 'Share' button or interactive mini-programs that may run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.
